He actually did it.
This is the Ark of Sirius?
The light...
That's the mountain we were headed to.
We need to catch up with them quickly.
Yes!
It's about time you started listening to your master.
Yuliy...
Mikhail, end the life of the Sirius with your own hands,
and then bring the bloodstained Ark to me.
If I'm to live
by inertia
There's probably nothing
wrong with giving up
But I don't want the night stolen from me
The moon shines down on me as if to comfort my shuttered heart
I'm left with only a cold blade
I'm just losing myself
I'm searching
Just like this planet that's lost everything
I don't think that I'm always right
But I'm not going to regret what I do now
Making just one wish, I fade into the night
Yuliy!
What, you guys are here too?
Hey, that's—
Oh, this?
I found it on the way here in an abandoned vehicle.
This wireless telegraph is something you need, isn't it?
You're...
Well, then.
Yuliy.
Did you get the Ark?
So this is it.
This is the Ark?
All for the sake of this thing...
Humans and vampires hunted it so feverishly,
and Dad sacrificed his life to seal it away.
Yuliy...
I'd like to hear more, but we don't have time for a long conversation.
He's right!
There's a huge airship outside!
That would be Yevgraf's.
The bastard was waiting for Yuliy to undo the seal.
The vampires, huh?
Everyone, let's run—
As the last living Sirius,
I need to settle the score myself.
Yuliy...
Stop right there, Yuliy.
I don't care if you go on a suicide mission,
but you're going to have to leave the Ark here.
You're...
We're almost to Karafuto!
Just fly us straight to the mountain range.
Roger!
First Dogville, and now Karafuto.
Yuliy sure is making us go to a lot of trouble.
Might I ask why you sound so happy while saying that?
Well, I am looking forward to it.
I always love a good rampage.
Yeah, yeah.
Not ready to open up, huh?
Shut up and fly!
Don't do anything too reckless, Yuliy.
Bishop?
So you're finally showing your true colors,
Mr. British Intelligence.
I guess Japanese Intelligence shouldn't be taken lightly.
You needed to lead him here and have him undo the Ark's seal.
Was that why you brought him to meet Captain Akasaka?
Yeah, it was the most roundabout thing I've ever done in my life!
But if only a Sirius could undo the seal, what else could I do?
I had no idea that Britain had gathered that much information on the Ark.
The whole world has its eyes on that Ark.
I was just the first to get here.
You can drop the act now, Bishop.
Huh?
I'd already noticed.
That you weren't a Jaeger,
and that you certainly aren't a British spy anymore.
What do you mean?
Oh?
So you knew all along?
A vampire?
Yuliy.
If you knew I was a vampire,
why did you agree to work with me?
Because of your eyes.
In your eyes I saw regret from not being able to save your team,
and guilt from outliving them by getting turned into a vampire.
I want to find the Ark before Yevgraf does,
break it before his very eyes, and then break him.
At that moment, I didn't detect even the slightest trace of lies or deceit in your eyes.
I couldn't help but try believing in you.
Believe?
What kind of tripe...
Good grief.
Can't hide anything from you.
All my dead buddies...
I can't get their faces out of my head.
And now that I'm a vampire, I could have them stuck in there for all eternity now.
Fortunately for me, there's that weird-ass disease going around.
Even if I don't lift a finger, all of them,
including me, will just drop dead.
Almost sounds too good to be true.
But now the Ark of Sirius is in the mix,
which might be able to do something about it.
Like hell I'm going to let them get it!
You need to settle the score yourself?
This isn't just your problem anymore!
Both me and these two are already involved!
Stop trying to play the big action hero by yourself.
Let me settle my score too.
Understood.
Lend me a hand.
Now we're talking.
You're going to work with a vampire?
Not with a vampire.
With Bishop.
I found Yuliy!
Where's Uncle Cowboy?
Is he dead?
Who cares about him, anyway?
Damn brat.
If things get bad, it's going to be every man for himself, okay?
Yuliy, look, look!
We brought Misha!
We can finally all play together!
Right?
Brother?
Give me...
the Ark.
the Ark!
Are we going to play battle-to-the-death?
Let me join, too!
Brother, what happened?
Can you not hear me?
That's right!
Misha wouldn't listen to
Lord Yev, so he got punished!
He'll be like this until Lord Yev tells him he can stop.
It's the blood pact.
Vampires can't disobey the master that made the pact with them.
He let Misha do whatever he wanted before.
It's Misha's fault for getting too full of himself.
Shit!
Wait for us!
That idiot!
Why's he leaving us behind?
Come on, run!
Keep going! You can't get away!
Aw, he got caught.
Give me...
the Ark.
Wake up, Brother!
Give me...
the Ark!
What are you—
The Ark is...
It's shining!
Thanks, Misha!
You keep playing with Yuliy!
We'll be back after we give this to Lord Yev!
Bishop?
What, you're still hanging around?
Your job's already—
Yuliy!
Leave the Ark to me!
Bishop...
I talked to Dad.
I found out everything.
What the Ark is.
The reason that Dad left Dogville with the Ark.
And I made a promise to him.
I promised to prove...
I'm going to prove that we can achieve the new pride of the Sirius that Dad yearned for!
We'd only hold him back if we tried to help.
Let's move.
Brother...
Yuliy.
If I ever end up like him,
I want you to be the one to kill me.
Brother!
Do I have to kill you here?
Kill you with my own hands?
Yuliy...
Yuliy!
Why are you here?
You can see me now?
It was only you!
All we needed was for you,
the last Sirius, not to step foot in here!
So why?
Brother...
I had to be here!
I had to meet Dad and undo the Ark's seal!
Bishop!
Why the hell did you kill Larissa? You're one of us!
It's not like I ever wanted to be!
Eternal life?
Becoming a "more noble" lifeform?
That's worth less than shit to me!
How can you say that after you made the blood pact?
Why would I want to suck blood for the rest of my life? I'm not a goddamned mosquito!
Babies get to suck on better stuff!
Because of the ancient laws of the Sirius,
any who learned of the Ark or wished to take it
were to be buried along with their knowledge.
Dad sealed the Ark because he thought that we'd never be able to coexist with other races if it were around.
But he was missing the bigger picture!
The Ark is the pride of the Sirius.
It's not something we should seal!
It's something that should exist as part of our pride!
That's why I'm going to face this world!
That's what I decided!
No!
You can't do that!
Why?
That's what it means to live with the Ark!
That was my promise to Dad!
I made a promise too!
I swore I would protect you!
I don't give a damn about the Sirius or the Ark!
You don't need to do anything!
All of that is my duty!
I should have done it, not you.
Brother...
I'm your older brother!
Becoming a vampire didn't change that.
I was always worried about you.
All ten years.
So am I.
I'm your brother too!
You have a little brother who loves you!
Yuliy...
How could I do nothing when my brother is suffering so much?
Yuliy!
Brother!
You...
Don't glare at me like that.
I'll send you chasing right after your partner.
I want to break it right here and now, but I don't think he'd be very happy about that.
Beautiful!
From its radiance, I can see that it received the blood of a Sirius, as the ancient text instructed.
Do not handle it roughly.
The loss of what you are holding would not be something you could make up for with your death.
Yuliy,
let go.
Just leave me.
Yuliy!
No! We're staying together even if you try to fight me off.
You're as stubborn as ever.
But you know...
We're not going to be able to be together for too long.
Are you—
Oh, you know about it?
The fatal disease that only vampires can catch.
There was no other way for me to escape the blood pact.
But...
Bishop!
Hey, Yuliy.
So you're Mikhail's little brother.
You have my thanks for unsealing the Ark.
Outstanding work.
Were you too excited to wait in the ship like a good boy, Yevgraf?
So he's...
I got bored of waiting for you.
It's been a very long time since my patience last failed me.
Sorry, Yuliy.
I guess in the end I couldn't help you much.
But lemme tell you.
When you talked about believing in me,
and about not working with a vampire,
but working with me,
I was pretty damn happy.
Bishop...
Listen up, Yuliy.
When you're beating the hell out of Yevgraf, make sure you hit him a few times for—
What a foolish man.
Deemed worthy by the blood pact,
but unable to accept it.
Mikhail, it seems you're cut from the same cloth.
Did you suck the blood of the infected?
Yeah.
Now, I'll finally be able to kill you.
I'm impressed that you can bluster while teetering so obviously on the edge of death.
All for your darling brother, eh?
However, playing with you comes after the release of the Ark.
The Ark will awaken from its long slumber and be opened!
For the first time in five thousand years, the knowledge of the Sirius will be made manifest!
I feel truly fulfilled.
Surely the souls of the wolves who died in Dogville will feel the same way.
Yuliy Jirov,
there is no end to my gratitude toward you.
When I obtain the wisdom of the Ark,
I'll let you stay by my side as a pet dog.
You'll be the last of the Sirius breed.
I'll take very good care of you!
You bastard!
I see you're just a mangy wolf, after all.
I suppose you'd prefer dying as you crawl on the ground!
Yevgraf!
Very well, then!
That will be a very Sirius-like end.
Yuliy!
Help those two deal with the ones here.
I'll go after Yevgraf!
This is all because I took the Ark from you.
If I don't make up for that,
then what kind of big brother am I?
You're in no condition to do that!
I'll—
Yuliy!
Just listen to me for once!
You can't!
At least take me—
Gentlemen, can we deal with more immediate problems before you have your sibling's quarrel?
I don't think that it's going to be very easy.
True enough.
Farewell.
Die with honor.
V Shipping?
Is that Mister Willard?
Professor?
Everyone!
Yuliy! Kept you waiting, huh?
I told you to bring us through gently!
Let's make this performance a loud one.
Hell yeah! Here we go for another pass!
Son of a gun!
Brother?
Brother!
Wait!
I'm coming to—
Yuliy!
I believe in you!
May victory be yours!
Thank you, Ryouko!
Did he just call me by my...
This giant won't get the hell off of us!
Fallon, throw him off!
Don't ask the impossible!
I can barely keep us in the air!
Yevgraf has obtained the Ark.
He's on that airship.
Yuliy's following him.
Fly toward the airship!
If you don't mind bringing the goliath beetle up there with us, no problem!
I suppose this is as far as we can follow them.
The Ark of Sirius that has existed since time immemorial...
The time for its canopy to open has finally come!
The Ark will become my body,
and my body will become the Ark.
After five thousand years, you will manifest today!
I will...
I will become the Ark of the Sirius—
No, the Ark of the Vampires!
The canopy has opened!
What an unbearable end
I breath out, breath out, breath out, and stop
As I'm fleeing from this cruel world, I fall into a deep sleep
I hide behind the words "I'm doing my best"
But in the end I do nothing but look back
Even when I feel like I've been able to change,
Eventually I realize that the only thing that's changed is the position of the stars
I find myself wondering if everything would feel better if I just broke
Before I fade away while thinking of you,
If I dig out all of my pain then I'll be able to shine like a real star
Will I find a beautiful dream?
This is how we embrace hope
The Ark can't be left in the hands of the likes of you!
I finally found it.
The thing that I have to do.
My own path!